[Waco] Branch Davidians: Mark Swett collection, Inclusive: 1921-2001, undated, Bulk: 1978-1993
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audio Recordings, 1976-1995, undated; 4
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: Australia Study, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: “The Foundation”, October 1989 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (1 of 3), January 15, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (2 of 3), January 15, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (3 of 3), January 15, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider, January 16, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (1 of 3), January 19, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (2 of 3), January 19, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (3 of 3), January 19, 1990 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: Marc Breault: Intro to Vernonite Theology, May 23, 1991 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: ATF Van, February 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Theology, April 14, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: Sex, April 25, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: General, March 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: Theology, March 31, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: “Talks with David about 2/28”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: NPR Radio: Barnett Report: Uncut, May 12, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: NPR Radio: Barnett Report, May 12, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan: “Eden”, October 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan: “Lust”, October 10, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan: Theology and Passover, March 23, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: Mt. Carmel: “A Day of Information”, April 17, 1994 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: Call to FBI, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: General, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: Dr. Phil Arnold and Dr. Jim Tabor, April 1, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: Catherine M., undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: Radio, March 15, 1993; March 17, 1993; and April 21, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: Negotiations, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, October 13, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: General (1 of 3), March 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: General (2 of 3), March 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: General (3 of 3), March 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: Wayne with David Koresh about 2/28, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: ATF and David Koresh, February 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: ATF, Channel 18 from 12:25 to 12:56, February 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: ATF, 9:48-10:20, February 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, March 28, 1993 and April 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: Dr. Arnold and Livingston Fagan, March 28, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, April 14, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: Dr. Arnold (1 of 2), March 29, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: Dr. Arnold (2 of 2), March 29, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, March 31, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, April 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: General, March 11, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: CFR, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, April 18, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan, April 10, 1993 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh on KRLD Radio Interview, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: Feast Days (1 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Feast Days (2 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: “The Name of God”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: “Confusion 1”, July 18, 1987 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: “King of the North” (1 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: “King of the North” (2 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: “The Daily”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: “God’s Holy Mountain”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: “Holy Mountain” and “Holy Spirit”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: “Holy Spirit”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: Daniel 11-12, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: Copy of Wisconsin, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: “This Ain’t No Cowboy’s Religion”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: “Bookshelf Religion”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: Washington, D.C., undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: Music, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: Moving Cars, April 18, 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: Last Recorded Words of David Koresh, April 16, 1993 and April 18, 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: Lt. Lynch, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: Department of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearm Radio Van, February 28, 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: Department of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearm Shooting, February 28, 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: Department of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearm Radio Van # 2, February 28, 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: Livingston Fagan to Dr. Arnold, March 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: Joyce Sparks Interview with David Koresh, April 2, 1992 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: “Mad Man in Waco”, 1987 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: Ben Roden Burial in Jerusalem, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: George Roden, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “What is Truth?”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (1 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: Schneider (2 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: “Face to Face”, March 1993 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: Lois Roden, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: Vernon Howell: Music, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: Sermon, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: Vernon Howell, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: 911 Waco 1A, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: 911 Waco 3A, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: 911 Waco 5A, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: 911 Waco 7A, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: 911 Call: 10:35-10:40 and 10:46-10:47, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: Channel 18: 911 Call: 10:50-11:21 and 11:21-11:52, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: SA61 #1, March 4-5, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: SA61 #2, March 5, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #1, March 5, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #2, March 5, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #3, March 15, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #4, March 5, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #5, March 7, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: SA62 #6, March 8, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #1, March 6, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #2, March 6, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #3, March 17, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #4, March 8, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #5, March 9, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #6, March 10, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #7, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #8, March 12, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: SA63 #9, March 11, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: SA64 #1, March 12, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: SA64 #2, March 13, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: SA64 #3, March 14, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: SA64 #4, March 15, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #1, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: SAWDTX 65, March 12, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #2, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #3, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #4, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #5, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #6, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #7, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #8, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #9, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #10, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #11, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #12, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #13, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #14, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #15, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 40)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #16, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 41)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #18, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 42)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #19, March 15, 1993 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 43)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #20 (1 of 2), March 8, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #20 (2 of 2), March 16, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #21 (1 of 2), undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #22 (2 of 2), undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #24, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #25, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: SA65 #26, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: SA66 #1, March 16, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #1, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #2: Tape 1 of 2, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #2: Tape 2 of 2, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #3, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #5, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #6, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #7, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #8, March 24, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #9, March 24, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #10, March 26, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #11, March 27, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #12, March 27, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: SA67 #13, March 28, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: SA68 #1, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: SA68 #2, March 23, 1993 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #1, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #2, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #3, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #4, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #5, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #6, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #7, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #8, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #9, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #10, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #11, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #12, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #13, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #14, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #15, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #16, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #17, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 40)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #18, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #19, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #20, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #21A, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #21B, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #22, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #23, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #24, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #25, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA69 #26, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #1, April 9, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #2, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #3, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #4, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #5, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #6: Tape 1 of 2, April 10, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #6: Tape 2 of 2, April 10, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #7, April 10, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #8, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #9, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #10, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #11, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #12, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #13, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #14, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #15 (1 of 2), April 15, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #15 (2 of 2), April 15, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #16, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #17, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #18, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #19, April 15, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #20, April 15, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #21, April 15, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #23, April 16, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #24 (1 of 2), April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #24 (2 of 2), April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #25 (1 of 3), April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #25 (2 of 3), April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #25 (3 of 3), April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #26, April 17, 1993 (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 40)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #28, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #29 (1 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #29 (2 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #31 (1 of 3), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #31 (2 of 3), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #31 (3 of 3), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #32 (1 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #32 (2 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #32 (3 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #32 (4 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 #32 (5 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 Survey 1, April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: SA72 Survey 2, April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: SAWDTX72, April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: Undated Music (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: #33, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #1 (1 of 4), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #1 (2 of 4), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #1 (3 of 4), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #1 (4 of 4), April 18, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (1 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (2 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (3 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (4 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (5 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (6 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #2 (7 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (1 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (2 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (3 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (4 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (5 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (6 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3 (7 of 8), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #3: Tape 8 of 8, April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 Survey 3, April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (1 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (2 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (3 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (4 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (5 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (6 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #4 (7 of 7), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #5 (1 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #5 (2 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #5 (3 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #5 (4 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: SA73 #5 (5 of 5), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #1, March 9, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #2, March 9, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #4, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #5, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #6, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #8, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #9, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #10, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #11, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #12, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #13, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #14, March 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: SA89B #15, March 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 3: 911 Call, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 4: 911 Call, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 5, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 20, April 15, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 21, April 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 26 (1 of 2), April 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 26 (2 of 2), April 17, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 27, April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 28 (1 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 28 (2 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 29 (1 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 29 (2 of 2), April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 30, April 18, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 30 (1 of 2), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 30 (2 of 2), April 19, 1993 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 67, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 85, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 124: Fire Bomb, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 40)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 66, undated (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 41)
  - Cassette Tape: “The Whole Bible Can Be Changed”, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Dale Littleton, March 4, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: SA23, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: NEGO (1 of 2), April 19, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: NEGO (2 of 2), April 19, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: “Excerpts”, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: General, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: General, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: General, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: SA22, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 85: DK Sparks, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: Radio Recording, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 12, March 11, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 15: Joyce Sparks, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: Surveillance (1 of 2), April 18-19, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: Surveillance (2 of 2), April 18-19, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 42, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 19, March 2, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 22, March 2, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 24, March 3, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 246, April 19, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: DK #3, February 28, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 22: R. Shirley, March 2, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 82, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 105: David Jones, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 199, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 87, March 7, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 88, March 7, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 94, March 8, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 223, April 14, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 77, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 243, April 18, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 130, March 16, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 80: Negotiations, March 7, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 34)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 129: Negotiations (1 of 2), March 15, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 35)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 129: Negotiations (2 of 2), March 15, 1993 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 36)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 80: David Koresh, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 37)
  - Cassette Tape: Mt. Zion, undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 38)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 104, March 10, 1994 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 39)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 95: Julie M., undated (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 40)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 77, March 7, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 198, April 8, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 64, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 175, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 92, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 233, April 15, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 243, April 18, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 231, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 208, April 11, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 9)